Welcome once again to A Severe Pain Center.
Friends, first of all,
I request you that if
you haven't subscribed to my channel yet, then
please subscribe to our channel by clicking this button. You can
see the bell icon next to it, so
as soon as I get the notification, it will definitely
reach you first. This push does
n't cost you any money, and with
one subscription, we get
even more practice in making videos. So, please,
you should definitely subscribe to our channel.
Friends, in this video, we are going to talk
about third-party insurance for two-wheelers through ICICI Lombard. Friends, first of all, we
take
Loota insurance on Thursday, that is, two-wheeler
insurance. Now the question arises,
what is third-party insurance? Third-
party insurance is a type of insurance in which the
insurance company compensates for any damage caused by your vehicle to the person in front of you. You do
n't have to pay for it. Additionally, it involves the
patience of both the driver and the owner. If you have any problem with
your vehicle while driving,  If any incident or accident happens, then
in this condition the insurance company will
also give you a compensation. Okay, so this
is third party insurance. So,
if you want to get third party insurance through this, then for a
wheeler, then we have
talked a little about how we will get it done.
And I would like to request one thing. If you have
not registered for your Wally Membership, then
I will give you its link in the description box.
Going from there, you can
become a part of our Will Remember This program.
Its fee is only ₹5. As soon as you pay
₹3, you can join our Veer and we will
release you. Through this, you will get your problem resolved. Your
subscription, Spice Money subscription, subscribe to your
question. I will give its link
in the description box. Going from there,
you must become a member of Excited. So, we
upload our video. The first thing you will have to do is to create your
alarm. If we click here,
click on login, then you will
catch the vehicle. You
set your new password here.
I have tissue paper here that the
man who holds the hospital here.  I click on it, you
can click on the point, as if we
will click on sign in, our account which is above will be shown in front of us,
as you can see,
our second account is opening here
and when our digital service portal
opens,
Ajay told
that third party insurance is a type of insurance in which
if someone gets into an accident with your car while driving, then the
insurance company takes care of it, if a
third party accident happens with the driver or the car owner in
which
they die or get injured, then this is
also taken care of by the insurance company, that is
for the third party,
in third party insurance the driver takes
care of the car owner, along with that the
company takes care of the damage caused to the person in front of you, so we have to do
this and I will tell you that through this channel, so first of all
you should
subscribe here, subscribe
here, you will click on the new party written here, I have done the
identity card of the insurance companies, here if you
look down, here you will find your CICI
long and thick third option,
I will see the process of consulting other companies  I will give
you the link of that in the description box. We are going to
talk to different companies, so
what we will do here is we
can subscribe to the intermediate, okay, so here
you can see that by
subscribing to this, there are products here,
so here because if you want to do
third party insurance for the first time, then here
you will click on the needle, this is written two wheeler, to get the
policy from this company
and this writing of cigarette UP
means third party insurance, okay, so
if we want to do two wheeler third party insurance in
advance, then click on that person
and check on get full course, okay,
as soon as you click on the pimpled court, the
details of the proposal will appear in front of you, you will have to
click here, okay, so
now see, here it has been called
that first of all you are going to
fill in the registration number of the vehicle, so as the
registration number of the vehicle
is written on it, like here you are going to register the question number,
okay, so in your
place, the number which is on the clock, you have to
subscribe here,
as you can see that
Uttar Pradesh Subscribe Discover 125 cc
vehicle and here
you are ready to give stop injury from which date you
want to start your insurance,
you
can also select the date from this side to start your insurance here, okay
now there are six ways to start here, if
you want to start your policy on the 27th then
you can click on subscribe time
or you have to select from the delivery date,
you will do it there, okay
after this then come down and
in the option of your workout their physique channel, whether
you want only one policy, Jio 4G policy
or three companions policy,
you have to select that here,
okay so if you have saffron termite lick
or premature ejaculation and here whatever time you
want, for whatever time you want, you are doing it
here, okay
after this then the engine number, chassis number is
automatically filled,
where the engine number, chassis number is
not automatically refilled, you can go back and enter the engine
number, chassis number here, okay  The
number that is written on the RC plane,
you see it, but if you
remove the tehsil, if a number is written in the cup of tea, an
economic incentive package for the vehicle will be
offered, okay, if it is in the same condition,
if it does not feel automatically, it gets done
automatically, then you do
not need to change it, just
mix it once, okay, and after this,
this deal etc. has to be picked up automatically,
and here, friend, mix your word once, it
comes here, so it is done,
and after doing this, you can leave the description, it is
not necessary to do it, okay, then in the friend
registration side,
individual and corporate speech have been given in it,
individual means
if there is a vehicle in the name of any person, whether it is a
man, woman or anyone, then
if he subscribes, subscribe and it will be
with his name, then it will be scanned, so
if you subscribe to any company,
subscribe to the channel, many times it happens
that people have personal accidents, there are some people who are
war, they
subscribe to that
personal accident even before the situation of an accident.  They do this
through which if they meet with an accident then
their benefits are taken separately by the insurance companies, it is
not there in this, so
if any quick appointment happens then
first of all subscribe in that condition,
if you want to subscribe then you will have to subscribe,
okay now the screen does
not get appointed,
after this share, don't have a valid guy,
if the person does not have a driving license, only then
you apply this option,
however this option should always be left on,
candy crush should be applied on it,
subscribing to it means scrub,
if you subscribe then
definitely subscribe to the other person, if you
cut this, then whatever your ₹1
lakh subscription is, if you
cut it, then the insurance company will
give only six thousand, half will be there, hence one
should always keep it, okay and you can subscribe to this channel,
okay, so we appointed here,
okay, after that
if you subscribe to it here, there is no problem,
now the school is subscribed, okay,
see here the CR can come for the
9th party, its time is 1330,
okay  Now here you have to give the name of the next nominee, the
newly appointed one and the meaning of which is
if the driver dies then
it is his wife, parents, whoever, grh grh
grh, there is no problem, after that you have to
click on the earth meaning something here to arrest the customer,
like you click on continue,
here you will be asked to click on search,
see here you have to type
Mr and Miss and Mr Sunit and
metals is the latest option, the
subject is not doing any soft copy, that will be the
responsibility of the company, sorry, I mean
if you are ever doing any such vehicle
which belongs to any company, then
you will subscribe here, if it is a woman then
Mr Musannif, it is okay, you will
enter the name of the customer, definitely enter their data, if you do
not enter the date of birth then it will
not proceed further, okay, if you do not have an
address then you can enter an approximate one,
if a person is of this age then you can
definitely place it on that side, there is no problem,
okay, you can do this by halving the address here.
Let
Jitendra turn off the flashlights if you
want to do it then you can do the deadline and here you can loot and
fight, I will request it, if you
want to drop the destined toe then you
can extend it, yes you can sleep, you
can see, you have to enter it here and
enter the mobile number,
click it, like friend, read the survey will be done in
front of you, you can wake up, I am
making it for you, but still I will
show you, okay,
joint rotation, I am entering it here,
okay, any pin code comes in front of me, I
entered this pin code and
selected mine here, so all this has
come automatically, here I have the Pahalwan
song
MP4, deleted the mobile number, Darshan's
card, after that we
can click on the falling groundwater here, as soon as you click it will
come in front of you and
what you have to do to appoint you,
subscribe and subscribe, okay
now see how you can do this service
because let's come and
tell you the method of doing it, if you do
not want to directly, then here you can
ladies horse problem  Install it, the driver
's work is over, now you were going to get the car for ₹15
and now we have made the screen here,
now if we click then we subscribe,
Arun is appointed director here, in this
I do not have to do any danger of the person in front,
okay, if we want to
subscribe to the third tip,
subscribe,
I am serious,
today I will show you, like if you have not consumed it then
you should give a little more
books to the organizations,
see this and give feedback here, so this is the
way to make the bike cheaper, now
what will happen in this, in this condition you will
not get any clear from the driver and
in the episode of coming back by car, then
you will have to subscribe yourself, so if
you can do this, do
subscribe and subscribe to our channel
and at the same time
definitely subscribe to our channel.